<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid 19 Stats App</string>

    <string name="splashimage">splashImage</string>
    <string name="corona_virus_statistics">COVID\-19 UPDATE\nSTATISTICS</string>
    <string name="splashdescription">splashDescription</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary</string>
    <string name="regions">Countries</string>
    <string name="preventions">Preventions</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="countryName">KENYA</string>
    <string name="total_recoveries">Total Recoveries</string>
    <string name="today_cases">Today Cases</string>
    <string name="today_recoveries">Today Recoveries</string>
    <string name="today_deaths">Today Deaths</string>
    <string name="critical_cases">Critical Cases</string>
    <string name="date_updated">Date Updated</string>
    <string name="number_holder">1500</string>
    <string name="total_tests">Total Tested</string>
    <string name="wash_hands">Regularly and thoroughly clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand
        rub or wash them with soap and water. Why? Washing your hands with soap and water or using
        alcohol-based hand rub kills viruses that may be on your hands.
    </string>
    <string name="wear_mask">Masks can help prevent the spread of the virus from the person
        wearing the mask to others. Masks alone do not protect against COVID\-19, and should be
        combined with physical distancing and hand hygiene.
    </string>
    <string name="elbow_cough">Make sure you, and the people around you, follow good respiratory
        hygiene. This means covering your mouth and nose with your bent elbow or tissue when you
        cough or sneeze. Then dispose of the used tissue immediately and wash your hands. Why?
        Droplets spread virus. By following good respiratory hygiene, you protect the people around
        you from viruses such as cold, flu and COVID\-19.
    </string>
    <string name="social_distance">Maintain at least 1 metre \(3 feet\) distance between yourself and
        others. Why? When someone coughs, sneezes, or speaks they spray small liquid droplets from
        their nose or mouth which may contain virus. If you are too close, you can breathe in the
        droplets, including the COVID\-19 virus if the person has the disease.
    </string>
    <string name="hospital">If you have a fever, cough and difficulty breathing, seek medical
        attention, but call by telephone in advance if possible and follow the directions of your
        local health authority. Why? National and local authorities will have the most up to date
        information on the situation in your area. Calling in advance will allow your health care
        provider to quickly direct you to the right health facility. This will also protect you and
        help prevent spread of viruses and other infections.
    </string>
    <string name="trends">Keep up to date on the latest information from trusted sources, such as
        WHO or your local and national health authorities. Why? Local and national authorities are
        best placed to advise on what people in your area should be doing to protect themselves.
    </string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="total_recovered">Total Recovered</string>
    <string name="total_cases">Total Cases</string>
    <string name="world">World</string>
    <string name="africa">Africa</string>
    <string name="total_deaths">Total Deaths</string>
    <string name="kenya">Kenya</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection_available">No Internet Connection Available</string>
    <string name="connect_to_internet_to_get_updates">Connect To Internet To Get Updates</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="developerimage">developerImage</string>
    <string name="github">Github</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="gmail">Gmail</string>
    <string name="linkedIn">LinkedIn</string>
</resources>